DÁLCIO GARCIA

Luanda, Angola · +244 935 427 504

dalciomacuetegarcia@gmail.com · LinkedIn: http://www.linkedin.com/in/dalcio-garcia Portfolio: https://dalciogarcia.vercel.app/ · GitHub: https://github.com/dalcio

Passionate Web and Mobile Developer with 1+ years of experience. Excited to continually learn from others, growing more and more. Equipped with a diverse and promising skill set. Able to bring amazing product designs to life with testing and debugging processes. Proficient in a variety of technologies including JavaScript, TypeScript, NodeJS, React and React Native, HTML3, CSS and more, including popular frameworks like Redux, NextJS, Styled Components, Styled System and others. Able to effectively self-

manage during independent projects as well as collaborate in a team environment.

EXPERIENCE

NOV, 2021 – JAN, 2022

WEB DEVELOPER, OKUSSAKULA

I created the landing page with ReactJS and Give Birth System with NextJS for Okussakula Startup consuming from a backend API made with .Net Core.

MAR, 2021 - SEP, 2021

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER, ABASTEÇA STARTUP

I was responsible for developing the ecosystem of

Abasteça Startup. I created a website to manage Abasteça

Services with Next Js.

I also created two applications, one related with geolocation and the way to manage the Abasteca subsystems using Expo.

All applications were integrated with firebase.

MAR, 2021 - JUL, 2021

REACT NATIVE MOBILE DEVELOPER, BAT DEV

I was responsible for bringing a UI and UX design to life using Expo, a framework and platform for universal React apps. I built an application that involves concepts such as delivery, e-commerce and much more. I also use TypeScript to build the app.

OCT, 2020 - MAR, 2021

FRONT END MOBILE DEVELOPER, MOCHI NOIR

- I was responsible for creating a mobile application with React Native and Typescript.
- The application was based on delivery app using 3rd party libraries API and consuming a Restful API

back-end. I also wrote unit tests.

EDUCATION

MARCH 2017 – PRESENT GRADUATION, INSTITUTO SUPERIOR POLITÉCNICO DE TECNOLOGIAS E CIÊNCIAS

SKILLS

- HTML5 & CSS3
- JavaScript
- NodeJS
- ReactJS

- React Native & Expo
- TypeScript
- React Frameworks (Redux, NextJS, and others).

LANGUAGES

PORTUGUESE	NATIVE SPEAKER	ENGLISH	B2
FRENCH	A1		

HOBBIES

I like to run a little every day of the week to free my mind and improve my creativity. I also love food and cooking and I like to meditate to improve my self-control.